quest-global.com 2019-08-23

# Privacy Policy

_Introduction_

**QuEST Global Services Pte. Ltd**., together with its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, **“Company”** or **“We”** ) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website https://www.quest-global.com and the candidate portal located at https://krb-sjobs.brassring.com/TGnewUI/Search/Home/Home?partnerid=30174&siteid=5116 (collectively, the **“Website”** ) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party; or
  * any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see _Changes to our Privacy Policy_ below. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**_Children Under the Age of 13_**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@quest-global.com.

**_Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It_**

QuEST Global is fully committed to complying with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and has taken the necessary steps to meet the requirements of the regulation. If you wish to get more details, please contact [dataprotection_quest@quest-global.com](mailto:dataprotection_quest@quest-global.com)

Our Wesite can be browsed by any individual without providing any personal information. In certain circumstances when an individual want to register or logon to website, we collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, title, company address, e-mail address, telephone number or fax number (“ **personal information** “);
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as demographic information, including gender and occupation; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

**_Information You Provide to Us_** **.** The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of submitting a resume and job application. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website. If you are interested in the career opportunities at QuEST, please read the <QuEST Applicant Data Privacy Notice link> before submitting your job application to us.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

**_Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies_** **.** As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see _Choices about How We Use and Disclose Your Information_.

**_How We Use Your Information_**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own oods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please adjust your user preferences in your account profile). For more information, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_.

**_Disclosure of Your Information_**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. Personal information is not used or shared with any third party for marketing purpose without the consent of the data subject.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government, or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers or others.

**_Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising** **.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

**_Accessing and Correcting Your Information_**

You may send us an e-mail at info@quest-global.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

**_Data Security_**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address specified in your account or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**_Contact Information_**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us our email address [dataprotection_quest@quest-global.com](mailto:dataprotection_quest@quest-global.com)
